krazyglue.com 2018-05-04

# Krazy Glue Privacy Policy

Welcome! Krazy Glue recognizes the importance of customer privacy and the need to protect information that users of the krazyglue.com Website ("Website") provide to us. This Privacy Policy explains how we handle information we learn about you from your visits to this Website. Please read our complete Privacy Policy. Krazy Glue will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy, so please refer back to this page from time to time to view the current policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use this web site.

## Customer Data Collection, Use and Protection

In general, you can visit our Website without telling us who you are. Our Web servers, through Google Analytics, collect the domain names of visitors along with traffic data related to age, gender and interests. This information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, interests, etc. Krazy Glue uses this information to measure the use of our Website and to improve the content of our Website and improve the correspondence between Krazy Glue and its users. Visitors can opt out this data collection by going to https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.

There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name, e-mail address and mailing address. Such customer data assists Krazy Glue in serving the following purposes:

  * To help you quickly find services or information
  * To help us create Website content most relevant to you
  * To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information, and other new products or services from Krazy Glue
  * To allow you to participate in contests conducted through our Website

Krazy Glue uses your information only for these purposes, and Krazy Glue does not disclose your information to third parties in providing you with these services through our Website. If you are a child under the age of 13, we specifically request that you not submit any personal information to us through this Website.

However, please note that Krazy Glue will disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Krazy Glue on the Website; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Krazy Glue, or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of krazyglue.com or the public.

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy other companies or their assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that Krazy Glue or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.

Our retailer location services are provided by the Google Maps API. For more information reference Google Privacy Policy.

## Web Server Cookies and Log Files

Krazy Glue also uses cookies to identify different types of Website users. A cookie is a small piece of information that is sent by our Web server, stored on your PC's hard drive, and used by your Web browser. Krazy Glue uses cookies to identify the type of customers using our Website. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, or you may disable cookies altogether. However, if you disable cookies, you may not be able to use portions of the Krazy Glue Website. Like most standard Website servers, we use log files. This includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses etc. are tied to personally identifiable information to enable our Web based service.

## Surveys

At times, we conduct online surveys to better understand the needs and profile of our visitors. When we conduct a survey, we will let you know how we will use the information we collect from you.

## Links

Our Website may contain links to other sites such as Krazy Glue distributors and sales affiliates. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites. Any information you provide to one of these other websites will be governed by the privacy policy of that website, if any, and not by this Krazy Glue Privacy Policy.

## Children's Privacy (Under the Age of 13)

Krazy Glue takes children's privacy seriously. We do not seek to collect personal information about children through our Website. If we become aware that a person submitting personal information to us through any part of our Website is a child, we delete the information as soon as we discover it and do not use it for any purpose, nor do we disclose it to third parties. Since we do not seek to collect any personal information about children, and we delete information collected inadvertently as soon as we discover that a child has submitted it, we typically retain no information about children that could be reviewed or deleted. If a parent requests review or deletion of information about their child before we have discovered and deleted the information, we will of course honor that request.

## Contact Krazy Glue

Krazy Glue strives to protect customer privacy. Should you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via e-mail at comments@krazyglue.com, or write to:

Krazy Glue  
460 Polaris Parkway, Suite 500  
Westerville, Ohio 43082  
Attn: Consumer Response  
Email: comments@krazyglue.com

## Terms of Service

Krazy Glue, an Elmer’s brand, owns and operates several online platforms, including, but not limited to the KrazyGlue.com website, Facebook.com/KrazyGlue and Twitter.com/KrazyGlueExpert. By tagging @KrazyGlueExpert, #KrazyBigFix, #fixthefail, #WhenTheBeatDropsContest, #KGCountryContest or other Krazy Glue sponsored terms or by commenting, liking, posting or otherwise engaging with the Krazy Glue brand, you grant Krazy Glue a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, transferable, irrevocable and fully sublicensable right to use, reproduce, modify, distribute, publish, create derivative works from and publicly display your content in any media, now known or hereafter devised, for any purpose. You also permit Krazy Glue to use the name that you submit in connection with such content. The connecting content will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary. Krazy Glue takes no responsibility for any content submitted by other users that uses the aforementioned terms or is otherwise submitted to Krazy Glue and is not liable for said content.

## #KGCountryContest Rules

**SPONSOR:** Krazy Glue®, Inc. (Krazy Glue)  
460 Polaris Parkway, Suite 500  
Westerville, OH 43082

**ENTRY:** To enter the #KGCountryContest, Twitter users must share their favorite “krazy country” moments from the 2015 Country Music Awards* and tag @KrazyGlueExpert and #KGCountryContest on Twitter between 8 p.m. ET, Wednesday, November 4 and 8 p.m. ET Thursday, November 5. No purchase necessary to enter. Only one entry per person per Twitter account; multiple entries will not be considered. Anyone found to use multiple accounts to enter will be ineligible. Krazy Glue reserves the right to disqualify any person it finds to be tampering with the entry process.

**ELIGIBILITY:** This contest is open only to legal residents of the U.S. over the age of 18 who agree to Krazy Glue’s above Terms of Service. Employees of Krazy Glue and their immediate family members are not eligible. This contest is void where prohibited.

**WINNER SELECTION & NOTIFICATION:** One (1) winner who has met the entry and eligibility requirements will be chosen at random and will be contacted via Twitter by 8 p.m. ET Monday, November 9. Inability to contact with the winner within 48 hours of Krazy Glue’s first attempt to contact him/her on Twitter will result in disqualification and selection of an alternate winner.

**PRIZE:** The winner will receive a $300 gift card to Guitar Center and Krazy Glue product. (Guitar Center is not a sponsoring partner of this contest.) The total prize value will not exceed $400. The winner is responsible for all applicable local, state and federal taxes. Odds of winning depend on the number of eligible entries received.

**LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY:** Krazy Glue is not responsible for late, lost or misdirected entries or for any other technical malfunctions. If for any reason the contest is unable to run as planned, Krazy Glue reserves the right to cancel or modify the contest. Entrants further agree to release Krazy Glue from any liability resulting from or related to contest participation. 

*Krazy Glue is an advertiser, but not a sponsor of, the Country Music Awards. Country Music Awards is not a sponsor of or affiliated in any way with this contest.
